Register of the Socialist Workers Party records
Hoover Institution Archives
- FOURTH INTERNATIONAL ISSUANCES, 1930-1990
  - Fourth International. International Executive Committee (Box 5)
    - Minutes. Includes agenda, reports, resolutions and declarations (in English and French)
      - 1976 February 12-15 (Folder 33)
      - 1979 November 18 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - 1981 May 7-14 (Folder 2)
      - 1982 May 22-30 (Folder 3)
      - January 27, February 6, 1985 (Folder 4)
      - February 23-March 2, 1986 (Folder 5)
      - 1987 June 22-28 (Folder 6)
      - 1988 December 3-10 (Folder 7)
  - Fourth International. International Secretariat (Box 6)
    - Boletín Interno
      - Unnumbered (September), 1951 (Folder 1)
      - Unnumbered (July), 1962 (Folder 2)
      - Unnumbered (n.d.), 1963 (Folder 3)
    - Bulletin d'Information
      - Unnumbered (November 1), 1952 (Folder 4)
      - No. 5 (March), no. 6 April), no. 8 (September), 1962 (Folder 5)
    - Bulletin Intérieur
      - Vol. 1 no. 1 (May), no. 2 (May), no. 3 (May), no. 4 (July), no. 5 (August), no. 6 (September), no. 8 (October), no. 9 (November), no. 10 (December), 1946 (Folder 6)
      - Vol. 1 no. 11 (January); vol. 2 no. 12 (February); vol. 1 [sic] no. 13 (March); vol. 2 no. 14 (April), no. 15 (June), no. 16 (July), no. 17 (August), no. 18 (September), unnumbered (October), unnumbered (December), 1947 (Folder 7)
      - Unnumbered (November), 1948 (Folder 8)
      - Unnumbered (February), two unnumbered (May), unnumbered (October), unnumbered (November), three unnumbered (December), 1949 (Folder 9)
      - No. 1 (February), no. 2 (April), unnumbered (May 4), unnumbered (June), no. 5 (October), 1950 (Folder 10)
      - No. 1 (January), no. 2 (February), no. 3 (March), no. 4 (April), no. 5 (May), no. 6 (June), no. 8 (July), four unnumbered (September), unnumbered (December), 1951 (Folder 11)
      - No. 2 (March), no. 3 (April), no. 4 (May), no. 6 (July), unnumbered (October), 1952 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - No. 1 (January), no. 2 (January), no. 3 (February), no. 4 (April), unnumbered (April), no. 5 (May), no. 6 (July), unnumbered (October, including typed English translation), unnumbered (November), unnumbered (December), 1953 (Folder 2)
      - Unnumbered (January), unnumbered (February), unnumbered (March), unnumbered (October), 1954 (Folder 3)
      - No. 7 (November), 1955 (Folder 4)
      - Unnumbered (April, including holograph English translation), unnumbered (November), 1956 (Folder 5)
      - Unnumbered (February, including typed English translation), unnumbered (March), unnumbered (July), unnumbered (November), 1957 (Folder 6)
      - Unnumbered (January), no. 2 (June), 1959 (Folder 7)
      - Unnumbered (December), 1961 (Folder 8)
      - No. 2 (February), unnumbered (March), no. 7 (May), no. 9 (June), no. 13 (July), no. 14 (July), no. 15 (August), no. 16 (August), no. 17 (August), no. 18 (August), no. 19 (September), no. 20 (October), no. 23 (October), no. 27 (November), 1962 (Folder 9)
      - No. 31 (February), no. 33 (February, hand-corrected from no. 4), no. 35 (February), no. 36 (April), no. 37 (April), no. 38 (April), 1963 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Bulletin International. No. 1, (1938 August) (Folder 2)
    - Information Bulletin. Vol. 1 no. 21 (January 1), no. 22 (January 15), no. 23 (February 1), no. 24 (February 15), no. 25 (March 1), no. 26 (March 15), no. 27 (April 11); vol. 2 no. 1 (April 11), no. 2 (May 1), no. 3 (May 15), no. 4 (June 1), no. 5 (June 15), no. 6 (July 1, hand-corrected from no. 5), no. 7 (July 15), no. 8 (August 1), no. 9 (August 15), no. 10 (September 1), no. 11 (September 15), no. 12 (October 3), no. 13 (October 18), 1959 (Folder 3)
    - Internal Bulletin
      - Unnumbered (December), unnumbered (mid-December), 1947 (Folder 4)
      - Unnumbered (January), unnumbered (December), 1948 (Folder 5)
      - Unnumbered (July), 1949 (Folder 6)
      - Unnumbered (July), 1951 (Folder 7)
      - Unnumbered (April), two unnumbered (July), unnumbered (October), unnumbered (November), 1957 (Folder 8)
      - No. 1 (April), no. 2 (n.d.), no. 3 (April, Information Bulletin), no. 4 (June, variant title Information Bulletin), no. 5 (July), no. 1 [sic] (September), unnumbered (September), no. 6 (November), no. 7 (December), 1959 (Folder 9)
      - No. 1 (January), no. 8 [sic] (January), unnumbered (January), no. 3 (February), 1960 (Folder 10)
      - No. 2 (February), no. 8 (May), no. 11 (June), no. 12 (July), no. 14 (July), no. 22 (October), 1962 (Folder 11)
      - No. 37 (April), no. 38 (April), no. 39 (May), no. 40 (May), 1963 (Folder 12)
    - International Bulletin. Unnumbered, (1946) (Folder 13)
    - International Press Service
      - November 15, December 20, 1946 (Folder 14)
      - May 2, August 8, 1947 (Folder 15)
      - 1948 July 13 (Folder 16)
      - 1949 February 5 (Folder 17)
    - Internationalist (Box 9)
      - Vol. 3 no. 1 (November), no. 2 (mid-November, including supplement), no. 3 (December), no. 4 (mid-December, including supplement), 1959 (Folder 1)
      - Vol. 3 no. 5 (January); vol. 4 no. 2 (mid-January), no. 3 (February), no. 4 (February 15), no. 5 (March 1), no. 6 (March 15), no. 7 (April 1), no. 8 (April 15), no. 9 (May 1), no. 10 (May 15), no. 11 (June 1, including supplement), no. 12 (June 15), no. 13 (July 1), no. 14 (July 15), no. 15 (August 1), no. 16 (mid-August), no. 17 (October), no. 18 (November), 1960 (Folder 2)
      - Unnumbered: February 5, 13, 21, 27; March 6, 13, 27; April 4, 11, 24 (in French); May 15; July 4, 25 (last issue published by Fourth International United Secretariat), 1963 (Folder 3)
    - Minutes (in French and English)
      - September 7, 16, 1938 (Folder 4)
      - February 25, May 6, July 9, 1939 (Folder 5)
      - November 9-10, 20, December 2, 16, 27, 1946 (Folder 6)
      - January 4, 15, 27, February 5, 18, March 4, 12, 24, April 8, 22, 24, May 5, 8, 19, 21, June 5, 12, 19, 26, July 8, 18, September 6, 24, October 1, 8, 14, 25, November 3, 14, 18, 25, December 1, 16, 23, 1947 (Folder 7)
      - January 9, June 3, 8, 25, July 1, 16, 22-23, August 11, 19, 28, September 3, 14, 27-28, October 6, 15, 23, 1948 (Folder 8)
      - 1949 September 18 (Folder 9)
      - September 13-15 (enlarged session), 1950 (Folder 10)
      - June 22 (European Bureau), 25, July 21-22, September 29 (European Bureau), 29-30, 1962 (Folder 11)
      - 1963 March 17-18 (Folder 12)
      - Lists. Lists of minutes of the International Secretariats of the Fourth International and its predecessors, 1930-1939 (Folder 13)
    - Service d'Information et de Presse. New series, no. 1 5), (1938 October (Folder 14)
    - Service de Presse. No. 4, (1950 July-August) (Folder 15)
    - Service International de Presse., 1951 March (Folder 16)
  - Fourth International. International Secretariat. Deutsche Kommission. Diskussions-Tribune. Vol. 1 no. 1, (1947 June) (Folder 17)
  - Fourth International. International Committee
    - Bulletin (in French)
      - Unnumbered (n.d.), no. 1 (December 28), 1953 (Folder 18)
      - No. 2 (February 26), no. 3 (May 28), no. 4 (May 28), no. 5 (December 15), 1954 (Folder 19)
    - Internal Bulletin. No. 1, (1960) (Folder 20)
    - International Bulletin
      - No. 6 (n.d.), 1961 (Folder 21)
      - No. 9 (n.d.), no. 10 (n.d.), 1962 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - No. 13 (n.d., hand-corrected from no. 11), no. 14 (n.d.), 1963 (Folder 2)
    - International Correspondence. Vol. 1 no. 1, (1967 February 6) (Folder 3)
    - Minutes. Includes agenda and resolutions (in English and French)
      - 1954
        - January 10-11 (Folder 4)
        - May 11 (Folder 5)
        - August (Folder 6)
        - November 6-9 (Folder 7)
      - May 20-21, June 10-12, 1955 (Folder 8)
      - 1958 June (Folder 9)
      - 1961
        - July 28-29 (Folder 10)
        - December 2-3 (Folder 11)
      - 1962
        - August 25-26 (Folder 12)
        - October (Folder 13)
  - Fourth International. Parity Committee (International Secretariat and International Committee). Minutes., 1962 September 2 (Folder 14)
  - Fourth International. United Secretariat
    - Boletín de Información
      - No. 1 (December), 1968 (Folder 15)
      - No. 3 (July), no. 4 (November), 1969 (Folder 16)
      - No. 5 (February), no. 6 (March), no. 7/8 (April-May), no. 9/10 (June-July), no. 11 (August), no. 12 (September), no. 13 (October), no. 14/15 (November-December), 1970 (Folder 17)
      - No. 16 (January), no. 17 (February), no. 18 (March-April), no. 19 (May), no. 20 (June), no. 21 (October), no. 25 (November), no. 26 (December), 1971 (Folder 18)
    - Boletín de Informaciónes Internacionales
      - Unnumbered (n.d.), 1971 (Folder 19)
      - No. 2 (September), no. 3 (October), no. 4 (October), 1973 (Folder 20)
      - No. 5 (January), no. 6 (January), no. 7 (August), no. 8 (August), 1974 (Folder 21)
    - Boletín Interno de Debate Internacional [ Inprecor]. New series, no. 1 no. 2 (June), (1982 March) (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Boletín Interno de Discusión Internacional
      - No. 1 (January), no. 3 (January), no. 4 (June), 1983 (Folder 9)
      - No. 8 (June), no. 9 (August), no. 10 (November), no. 11 (November), no. 12 (November), 1984 (Folder 10)
    - Bulletin Intérieur (Box 11)
      - Vol. 1 no. 2 (October), no. 4 (December), unnumbered (December, including typed English translation), 1963 (Folder 1)
      - Unnumbered (February), no. 1 (May), no. 7 (June), unnumbered (June, including typed English translation), 1964 (Folder 2)
      - Unnumbered (March), unnumbered (May), unnumbered (July), unnumbered (August), no. 6 (November), unnumbered (n.d.), 1965 (Folder 3)
      - No. 1 (January), no. 3 (March), no. 4 (March), no. 5 (March), no. 10 (July), no. 12 (December) [variant title Bulletin Intérieur d'Informations Internationales sur le Travail Jeune], no. 12 bis (December, in English [variant title Bulletin Intérieur d'Informations Internationales sur le Travail Jeune], 1966 (Folder 4)
      - No. 1 (January) [variant title Bulletin Intérieur International d'Informations sur le Travail Jeune], no. 2 (February), no. 3 (May), no. 4 (June), no. 5 (n.d.), no. 6 (July), 1967 (Folder 5)
      - No. 5 (n.d.), no. 6 (n.d.), 1968 (Folder 6)
      - No. 12 (February), no. 14 (March), no. 15 (March), no. 16 (March), no. 18 (April); new series, no. 1 (September), unnumbered (n.d.), 1969 (Folder 7)
      - No. 2 (n.d.), no. 3 (n.d.), no. 5 (April), no. 6 (April), no. 7 (July) [variant title Bulletin Interne], no. 11 (July) [variant title Bulletin Interne], no. 13 (September), no. 14 (October), no. 15 (October), no. 17 (November), 1970 (Folder 8)
      - No. 21 (July), three unnumbered (n.d.) [variant title Bulletin de Conférences de Travail Européennes], 1971 (Folder 9)
    - Bulletin Intérieur International de Discussion [ Inprecor/Intercontinental Press] (Box 55)
      - Unnumbered (December), 1980 (Folder 11)
      - New series, no. 1 (March), no. 2 (April), no. 3 (May), no. 4 (August), 1982 (Folder 12)
      - No. 5/6 (January), no. 7 (March), no. 8/9 (May-June), no. 10 (August), no. 11 (September), no. 12 (December), 1983 (Folder 13)
    - Cahier d'Information--Europe/European Information Bulletin. No. 1, no. 2, no. 3, no. 4, no. 6 (all, 1988) (Folder 14)
    - Documentation Internationale. No. 1 2 volumes), unnumbered (December), (1972 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Informaciónes y Documentos. No. 27 (January), no. 28 (February), no. 29 (March), no. 30 (April), no. 31 (May), no. 32 (June), no. 33 (September), no. 34 (October), no. 35 (November), no. 36 (December-1973 January), 1972 (Folder 2)
    - Internal Bulletin
      - No. 1 (July), 1963 (Folder 3)
      - 1964
        - Vol. 2 no. 5, (January) (Folder 4)
        - Unnumbered, (February) (Folder 5)
        - Unnumbered, (December) (Folder 6)
      - 1965
        - Unnumbered (March), unnumbered (April), unnumbered (June) (Folder 7)
        - No. 5 (September), no. 7 (October), no. 9 (November) (Folder 8)
      - No. 2 (January), no. 4 (March), no. 8 (May), no. 11 (December), 1966 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - No. 7 (October), 1967 (Folder 2)
      - No. 1 (n.d.), no. 2 (n.d.), no. 8 (n.d.), no. 9 (n.d.), 1968 (Folder 3)
      - No. 13 (March), no. 17 (March), 1969 (Folder 4)
    - International Internal Information Bulletin [ International Viewpoint]. Unnumbered, (1984 February) (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Minutes. Includes agenda, preparatory material and resolutions (in English and French) (Box 13)
      - June 29-30, August 31-September 1, September 28-29, November 9-10, December 21-22, 1963 (Folder 5)
      - January 25-26, February 14, March 14-15, April 11-12, June 20-21, July 25-26, September 12-13, October 17-18, November 14-15, December 5-6, 1964 (Folder 6)
      - February 13-14, March 20-21, April 24-25, May 22-23, June 20-21, July 26, August 21-22, September 25-26, October 30-31, 1965 (Folder 7)
      - January 8-9, January 13-14, February 12-13, March 12-13, April 16-17, May 21-22, August 20-21, October 1-2, November 5-6, December 3-4, 1966 (Folder 8)
      - January 7-8, January 30, April 29-30, May 27-28, July 24-25, August 29-30, September 23-24, October 28-29, November 11-12, December 1-2, 1967 (Folder 9)
      - January 13-14, February 5, March 2-3, April 6-7, May 4-5, June 1-2, June 29-30, August 3-4 (Enlarged Bureau), August 31-September 1, September 29-30, November 9-10, December 7-8, 1968 (Folder 10)
      - January 18-19, February 8-9, March 8-9, April 20, May 17-18, June 14-15, July 19-20, August 23-24, September 20-22, October 25-26, November 22-23, December 19-20, December 25, 1969 (Folder 11)
      - January 31-February 1, March 8-9, April 4-5, May 9-10, June 5-6, July 4-5, August 5-7 (Bureau), September 19-20, October 24-25, November 20, December 27-28, 1970 (Folder 12)
      - January 23-24, February 20-21, March 20-21, April 17-18, May 22-23, June 26-27, July 24, August (Bureau), September 25-26, October 29-November 1, November 29-30, December 21-22, 1971 (Folder 13)
      - February 5-6, March 4-5, April 15-16, May 20-21, May 30-31, July 8-10, August 19-20 (Bureau), September 23-25, October 28-29, December 1, December 5-7, 1972 (Folder 14)
      - January 20-21, February 24-25, April 7-8, May 14-15, July 9-10, August 21 (Extended Bureau), September 17-19, October 23-24, November 27-28, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - January 15-16, March 16, April 20, May 29-30, July 3, September 7-8, October 12-13, November 16-17, December 17, 1974 (Folder 2)
      - January 24, March 15-16, April 19-20, May 31-June 1, July 5-6, September 1-2, October 4-5, November 23-24, December 22-23, 1975 (Folder 3)
      - January 24-25, February 12, February 15, March 13-14, April 24-25, May 22-23, July 3-4, August 2, September 11-12, October 16-17, November 13-14, December 20-21, 1976 (Folder 4)
      - February 5-7, March 22-24, April 30-May 2, June 1-3, July 21-22, September 15-16, October 29-31, December 13-14, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - January 27-29, April 1-2, July 4-6, November 6-9, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - March 31-April 4, May 27-30, July 2-4, September 29-October 4, 1979 (Folder 2)
      - January 26-29, March 27-30, May 30-June 1, July 18-20, September 25-27, November 28-30, 1980 (Folder 3)
      - January 30-February 1, March 27-29, June 29-30, November 12, 1981 (Folder 4)
      - January 7-10, March 11-14, May 21-22, May 30, September 2-3 (Enlarged Bureau), October 6-10, 1982 (Folder 5)
      - January 24-27, March 12-14, May 27-30, September 7-8 (Enlarged Bureau), October 20-24, 1983 (Folder 6)
      - January 26-29, May 10-13, September 6-9, November 8-11, 1984 (Folder 7)
      - (Bureau), April 23-27, June 3-4, June 17-21, September 30-October 5, December 16-20, 1985 (Folder 8)
      - February 22, April 29-30, June 9-13, September 29-October 1, December 15-19, 1986 (Folder 9)
      - March 2-6, June 21, November 2-6, 1987 (Folder 10)
      - March 21-27, June 20-24, 1988 (Folder 11)
      - 1989 June 27-July 1 (Folder 12)
    - World Politics. Vol. 1 no. 3, (1965 March 31) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Fourth International. United Secretariat. European Bureau. Minutes, Includes reports (in English and French), 1973
    - March 17-18 (Folder 6)
    - April 28-29 (Folder 7)
  - Fourth International. International Revolutionary Marxist Tendency (Box 56)
    - Lettre Internationale pour l'Autogestion. No. 7, (1989 May) (Folder 13)
    - Political Letter. No. 6 second fortnight), (1967 January (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Fourth International miscellaneous publications
    - Acerca de la Discusión en el IX Congreso Mundial de la IV Internacional (pamphlet), 1973 (Folder 9)
    - Argentina y Bolivia: Un Balance (pamphlet), 1973 (Folder 10)
    - Boletín de Sociología del Siglo XX. No. 8, (1973) (Folder 11)
    - Boletín de Sociología Internacional. No. 1, (1974) (Folder 12)
    - Correspondance Internationaliste. No. 20, (1940 April 23) (Folder 13)
    - Informations Internationales. No. 3, (1962) (Folder 14)
    - Vérité [New York]. No. 1 (April), no. 3 (September), no. 4 (October), 1941 (Folder 15)
- CHRONOLOGICAL FILE, 1929-1989
  Records of the Socialist Workers Party's interactions with the Fourth International and its predecessors, not classified by geographical area, including correspondence, notes, memoranda, reports, proposals, theses, resolutions, declarations, statements, manifestos, appeals and circulars. Arranged chronologically.
  - Includes correspondence of Leon Trotsky, 1929 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Includes correspondence of Leon Trotsky, 1930 (Folder 2)
  - Includes correspondence of Leon Trotsky, 1931 (Folder 3)
  - Includes correspondence of Leon Trotsky, 1932 (Folder 4)
  - Includes correspondence of Leon Trotsky, report on Conference of Four of December 30, and material on Spain, Germany and the United States, 1933 (Folder 5)
  - Includes correspondence of Leon Trotsky, and material on Great Britain, Belgium, France and Germany, 1934 (Folder 6)
  - Includes correspondence of Leon Trotsky, and material on Belgium, France, Spain, the United States, and the London Bureau, 1935 (Folder 7)
  - Includes correspondence of Leon Trotsky, and material on Spain and the United States, 1936 (Folder 8)
  - Includes correspondence of Leon Trotsky, and material on Spain, Indochina, China, the United States, and the German group in exile, 1937 (Folder 9)
  - Includes correspondence of Leon Trotsky, and material on Great Britain, Poland, South Africa, the United States, and the murder of Rudolf Klement, 1938
    - February-June (Folder 10)
    - July-December (Folder 11)
  - Includes material on France, 1939 (Folder 12)
  - Includes material on France, 1940 (Folder 13)
  - Includes material on Argentina and Chile, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Includes material on Argentina and Europe, 1942 (Folder 2)
  - Includes material on Italy, 1943 (Folder 3)
  - Includes material on France, Indochina, China, and prospects for postwar Europe, 1944 (Folder 4)
  - Includes material on Chile, Great Britain, Belgium, France, Italy, Egypt, Palestine, India/Ceylon, Australia, the Spanish group in exile in Mexico, the Goldman-Morrow group in the United States, and the Nuremberg Trials, 1945
    - February-June (Folder 5)
    - July (Folder 6)
    - August-November (Folder 7)
    - December (Folder 8)
  - Includes material on Great Britain, Belgium, France, Austria, Germany, the Spanish group in exile in Mexico, the Goldman-Morrow group and the Workers Party in the United States, and the Nuremberg Trials, 1946
    - January-March (Folder 9)
    - April-May (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - June-July (Folder 2)
    - August-September (Folder 3)
    - October-December (Folder 4)
  - Includes material on Argentina, Great Britain, France, Germany, Greece, China, Mexico and the Spanish group in exile there, the Goldman-Morrow group and the Workers Party in the United States, the Ecole Internationale des Cadres, and colonialism, 1947
    - January-April (Folder 5)
    - May (Folder 6)
    - June (Folder 7)
    - July-September (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - October-December (Folder 2)
  - Includes material on Great Britain, France, Germany, Czechoslovakia, Yugoslavia, India/Ceylon, China, Japan, and the United States, 1948
    - January-June (Folder 3)
    - July-December (Folder 4)
  - Includes material on Great Britain, France, Italy, Yugoslavia, Indonesia, and Mexico and the Spanish group in exile there, 1949
    - January-May (Folder 5)
    - June-December (Folder 6)
  - Includes material on Italy, Germany, Yugoslavia, China, the United States, Ukrainians in exile, and the Korean War, 1950 (Box 19)
    - January-March (Folder 1)
    - April-December (Folder 2)
  - Includes material on France, the United States, and Nataliia Sedova Trotskaia in Mexico, 1951 (Folder 3)
  - Includes material on Bolivia, Great Britain, France, and Ceylon, 1952 (Folder 4)
  - Includes material on Great Britain, France, Germany, the United States, the Chinese group in exile, and the International Secretariat/International Committee split in the Fourth International, 1953
    - January-August (Folder 5)
    - September-October (Folder 6)
    - November (Folder 7)
    - December (Folder 8)
  - Includes material on Canada, Bolivia, Argentina, Great Britain, Denmark, the Netherlands, France, India, Ceylon, the Chinese group in exile, and the International Secretariat/International Committee split in the Fourth International, 1954 (Box 20)
    - January (Folder 1)
    - February (Folder 2)
    - March (Folder 3)
    - April-May (Folder 4)
    - June-December (Folder 5)
  - Includes material on Great Britain and France, 1955 (Folder 6)
  - Includes material on Chile, the Soviet Union, and Bulgarians in exile, 1956 (Folder 7)
  - Includes material on Great Britain, Spain, and Fourth International unity negotiations (including papers of Sherry Mangan), 1957 (Folder 8)
  - Includes material on Great Britain, Spain, the youth movement in the United States, and Fourth International unity negotiations (including papers of Sherry Mangan), 1958 (Folder 9)
  - Includes material on Great Britain and Greece, 1959 (Folder 10)
  - Includes material on Cuba, Great Britain, the Netherlands, Greece, Algeria, Ceylon, and Japan, 1960 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Includes material on Canada, Cuba, Jamaica, and Great Britain, and the Latin American Bureau of the Fourth International, 1961
    - January-August (Folder 2)
    - September-December (Folder 3)
  - Includes material on Canada, Cuba, Great Britain, Spain, Algeria, the international Pablo and Posadas factions, and Fourth International unity negotiations, 1962
    - January-July (Folder 4)
    - August-October (Folder 5)
    - November-December (Folder 6)
  - Includes material on Canada, Bolivia, Argentina, Great Britain, and reunification of the Fourth International, 1963 (Folder 7)
  - Includes material on Canada, Mexico, Cuba, Venezuela, Bolivia, Chile, Argentina, Great Britain, and the Pablo faction split from the Fourth International, 1964 (Folder 8)
  - Includes material on Canada, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Includes material on Cuba, Peru, Great Britain, France, Italy, Iran, Ceylon, and China and the Sino-Soviet dispute, 1966 (Folder 2)
  - Includes material on Bolivia, Great Britain, France, and Greece, 1967 (Folder 3)
  - Includes material on Cuba, Puerto Rico, Belgium, France, Czechoslovakia, and Ceylon, 1968 (Folder 4)
  - Includes material on Mexico, Peru, Bolivia, Argentina, Great Britain, Belgium, France, Czechoslovakia, Algeria, Nigeria, India, Ceylon, China, Japan, Australia, New Zealand, the United States, and the anti-Vietnam War movement, 1969
    - January-March (Folder 5)
    - April-September (Folder 6)
    - October-December (Folder 7)
  - Includes material on Canada, Great Britain, and France, 1970 (Folder 8)
  - Includes material on Great Britain and Czechoslovakia, 1971 (Folder 9)